# **JON YEATMAN**

jonlyeatman@gmail.com | 404-423-7274 | https://www.jonyeatman.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/jon-yeatman

## **SUMMARY**

Thorough and meticulous **Business Analyst/Administrator** passionate about helping businesses succeed. Former **small business owner** and certified **full-stack web developer**. Organized problem solver with a strong technical aptitude and ability to partner with leadership, sales, marketing, support and other important teams to maximize operations and interactions. Experience with various stages of the Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC) especially design, analysis, deployment and maintenance.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Honu Management Group**

Senior Operations Coordinator, Nov 2021 - Present

- Created an interactive dashboard and corresponding reports to improve workflow and manual documenting of inventory information
- Led a team of 4 to ensure productivity levels were met in accordance with pre-set turnaround times and internal and external customer service standards
- Prioritized projects/issues and allocated personnel to consistently meet productivity goals
- Managed projects that included maintaining issues logs, providing team performance feedback, facilitating
  work sessions to resolve issues, creating project work plans and writing status reports.
- Identified resources, activities, and tasks needed to produce each of the desired results.
- Analyzed operation processes to create and maintain efficiencies

## **Phoenix Custom Printing, LLC**

Founder & Director of Operations, 2018 - Present

- Oversaw the competitive bid and negotiation process with vendors and suppliers
- Maximized immediate turn-around by minimizing unnecessary overhead
- Partnered with local third-party vendors to create a streamline process for clients
- Quality relationship building with clients for trustworthy product delivery

#### **Lead Graphic Designer**

Superior Edge Leather Works, LLC, 2017 - 2019

- Consistently delivered close to 500 designs quarterly per clientele
- Optimized processes working with a variety of garments, inks and merchandise
- Streamlined production pipeline for multi-faceted items

## **Michgan Army National Guard**

Infantryman, 2013 - 2017

- Displayed a high-level of competence and professionalism under stressful situations
- Supervised, trained and ensured the safety and welfare of a 4-person team, maintaining a 100% safety record

### **EDUCATION**

## Michigan State University, East Lansing, MI

Certificate, Full-Stack Development, 2021

#### **OTHER**

**Technical Skills:** Microsoft Office, Salesforce, Relational Databases (MySQL), Tableau, SharePoint and advanced Microsoft Excel functions, Programming languages (Python, React, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery)

**Strengths**: Leadership, Project Management, Training and Instructing, Out-of-the-Box Thinking, Business-Strategy, Attention to Detail, Efficiency, Data Analysis